Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Miscellaneous, B.2.7.3.2.3
            - Mediterranean Sea, Africa north coast, B.2.7.3.2.3.7
              - 1658: Khaniá - Örmos Soúdhas - Réthimnon - Iráklion, 24th December 1954 (last correction 1958), 3524; blad
              - 1685: Venetico Island to Spetsai Island, 21st July 1908 (last correction 1963), 3525; blad
              - 1712: Plans on the coasts of Algeria and Tunisia, 14th November 1958 (last correction 1966), 3526; blad
              - 1719: Plans on the west coast of Italy, 8th April 1955, 3527; blad
              - 1731: Porto di Napoli, 31st December 1937 (revised 1962), 3528; blad
              - 1766: Cape Ferrat to Cape Bougaroni, 7th November 1871 (last correction 1959), 3529; blad
              - 1780: Barcelona to Napoli, 21st July 1967, 3530; blad
              - 1800: Malta to Cape Malea, including the Ionian Islands, 30th April 1894 (last correctioon 1961), 3531; blad
              - 1804: Cape St. Sebastian to Sète, 14th June 1894 (last correction 1959), 3532; blad
              - 1805: Sète to Marseilles, 27th August 1894 (revised 1961) (last correction 1962), 3533; blad
              - 1817: Sifnos, 29th June 1847 (last correction 1960), 3534; blad
              - 1832: Plans in the Kikládhes, 21st September 1956, 3535; blad
              - 1841: Civita Vecchia to Napoli, 23rd October 1893 (revised 1963), 3536; blad
              - 1842: Naples to Cape Bonifati, 19th March 1894 (last correction 1957), 3537; blad
              - 1848: Puerto de Málaga, 8th November 1963, 3538; blad
              - 1909: Cap IVI to Alger, 25th June 1894 (last correction 1959), 3539; blad
              - 1910: Algiers to Cape Bougaroni, 18th June 1894 (last correction 1957), 3540; blad
              - 1912: Tangier Bay and Harbour, 31st December 1936 (last correction 1957), 3541; blad
              - 1976: Cape Bonifati to Strait of Messina, 12th July 1894 (last correction 1959), 3542; blad
              - 1996: Rijeka (Fiume) including Luka Martinscica, 26th May 1950, 3543; blad
              - 2043: Santorin Island - Cristiani Islands, 4th April 1851 (last correction 1956), 3544; blad
              - 2051: Melos, Kimolos and adjacent islands - Port Melos, 6th November 1930 (last correction 1949), 3545; blad
              - 2051: Melos, Kimolos and adjacent islands, 6th November 1930 (last correction 1957), 3546; blad
              - 2070: Saloniki Bay, anchorage and Harbour, 11th June 1917 (last correction 1937), 3547; blad
              - 2070: Gulf of Thessaloniki, Thessaloniki Bay and Thessaloniki Harbour, 31st March 1950 (last correction 1953), 3548; blad
              - 2074: Cyprus, 24th May 1892 (last correction 1948), 3549; blad
              - 2074: Cyprus, 15th October 1954 (last correction 1957), 3550; blad
              - 2121: Cap de Fer to Îles Cani, 24th May 1963, 3551; blad
              - 2122: Bizerte to Capo San Marco, 24th May 1963, 3552; blad
              - 2158a: Mediterranean Sea - western sheet, 18th December 1883 (last correction 1955), 3553; blad
              - 2158b: Mediterranean Sea - eastern sheet, 18th December 1883 (revised 1960), 3554; blad
              - 2188: Plans on the coast of Syria and Turkey, 30th July 1926 (last correction 1953), 3555; blad
              - 2188: Ports and anchorages on the south coast of Turkey, 15th February 1957 (revised 1961), 3556; blad
              - 2428: Dragonera Island to Carril Bay including Palma Bay, 22nd April 1895 (last correction 1945), 3557; blad
              - 2428: Dragonera Island to Carril Bay including Palma Bay, 22nd April 1895 (last correction 1958), 3558; blad
              - 2428: Dragonera Island to Carril Bay including Palma Bay, 22nd April 1895 (last correction 1959), 3559; blad
              - 2429: The Dardanelles, 20th June 1952 (last correction 1953), 3560; blad
              - 2437: Cape Tres Forcas to Cape Ivi, 6th August 1895 (last correction 1928), 3561; blad
              - 2437: Cabo Tres Forcas to Cap Ivi, 6th August 1895 (last correction 1959), 3562; blad
              - 2536b: Crete - eastern part, 17th April 1858 (last correction 1958), 3563; blad
              - 2538: Approaches to Valletta Harbours and Marsaxlokk, 6th September 1957 (last correction 1961), 3564; blad
              - 2554: Rada e Porto di Livorno, 21st January 1946 (revised 1962), 3565; blad
              - 2555: Algiers (Alger), 17th February 1961, 3566; blad
              - 2573: Damietta to El Arish, 25th April 1930 (last correction 1957), 3567; blad
              - 2607: Marseille to Agay Road, 16th October 1893 (revised 1959), 3568; blad
              - 2608: Approaches to Toulon, 16th October 1893 (last correction 1956), 3569; blad
              - 2608: Approaches to Toulon, 16th October 1893 (last correction 1957), 3570; blad
              - 2609: Rade d'Agay to San Remo, 16th October 1858 (last correction 1957), 3571; blad
              - 2630: Alexandria to Port Said, 11th November 1925 (last correction 1961), 3572; blad
              - 2632: Anamur Burnu to Latakia including Iskenderun Körfezi, 25th November 1955 (last correction 1959), 3573; blad
              - 2632: Gulf of Iskanderún to Markhab, 29th March 1861 (last correction 1953), 3574; blad
              - 2633: Latakia to Sour, 27th August 1954 (last correction 1957), 3575; blad
              - 2634: Sour to El Arish, 6th November 1936 (last correction 1956), 3576; blad
              - 2668: Mersin Roadstead, 23rd January 1897 (last correction 1946), 3577; blad
              - 2681: Approaches to Alexandria and Abu Qir Bay, 4th November 1938 (last correction 1954), 3578; blad
              - 2711: Gulf of Quarnaro, 2nd April 1877 (last correction 1952), 3579; blad
              - 2713: Korcula to Kotor, 22nd January 1878 (last correction 1960), 3580; blad
              - 2717: Gibraltar to Alicante and Cape Spartel to Cape Ferrat, 20th January 1878 (revised 1962) (last correction 1963), 3581; blad
              - 2717: Cádiz to Barcelona, 3rd January 1969, 3582; blad
              - 2742: Bahia de Ceuta, 2nd April 1929 (last correction 1957), 3583; blad
              - 2753: Islands of Folégandros, Sikinos and Ios, 1st July 1863 (last correction 1954), 3584; blad
              - 2822: Gulfs of Napoule and Juan including Cannes and Antibes, 13th May 1905 (last correction 1958), 3585; blad
              - 2836a: Grecian Archipelago - southern sheet, 15th September 1863 (revised 1963), 3586; blad
              - 2836b: Grecian Archipelago - northern sheet, 15th September 1863 (last correction 1959), 3587; blad
              - 3036: Head of Bahia de Pollensa - Puerto de Palma, 10th March 1899, 3588; blad
              - 3119: Alexandria Harbour, 23rd December 1938 (last correction 1956), 3589; blad
              - 3119: Alexandria Harbour, 23rd December 1938 (last correction 1971), 3590; blad
              - 3220: Cape Ferrat to Bordighera - Port Monaco, 12th April 1902 (revised 1964), 3591; blad
              - 3276: Islas Ibiza and Formentera - Channels between Ibiza and Espalmador, 8th July 1902 (last correction 1948), 3592; blad
              - 3327: Kélibia to Tripoli, 25th July 1958, 3593; blad
              - 3346: Ez Zueitina, 1st August 1969, 3594; blad
              - 3350: Marsa El-Bréga, 24th May 1963 (revised 1964) (last correction 1965), 3595; blad
              - 3352: Port of Benghazi and approaches, 28th August 1934 (last correction 1954), 3596; blad
              - 3354: Sirte to Tolmeita, 19th November 1937 (last correction 1961), 3597; blad
              - 3354: Sirte to Tolemaide, 19th November 1937 (revised 1965), 3598; blad
              - 3355: Tolméta to Salûm, 19th November 1937 (revised 1960), 3599; blad
              - 3356: Salûm to Alexandria, 10th July 1942 (last correction 1949), 3600; blad
              - 3578: Eastern approaches to Strait of Gibraltar, 3rd December 1906 (revised 1959), 3601; blad
              - 3657: Mersa Tòbruch, 4th November 1949 (last correction 1964), 3602; blad
              - 3675: Ports and anchorages in Yugoslavia, 18th December 1953 (last correction 1956), 3603; blad
              - 3900: Punta del Mesco to Livorno, 31st October 1944 (revised 1959), 3604; blad
              - 3901: Punta Fortullino to Canale di Piombino, 31st October 1944 (last correction 1960), 3605; blad
              - 3905: Isola d'Elba, 31st October 1944 (last correction 1951), 3606; blad
              - 3906: Golfo di Follonica and approaches, 31st October 1944 (last correction 1951), 3607; blad
              - 3909: Punta Invrea to Nervi - Approaches to Genova, 1st December 1944 (last correction 1956), 3608; blad
              - 3910: Punta San Donato to Punta Invrea, 1st December 1944 (last correction 1955), 3609; blad
              - 3911: Capo Cervo to Capo di Noli, 1st December 1944 (last correction 1956), 3610; blad
              - 3912: San Remo to Capo delle Mele, 1st December 1944 (last correction 1957), 3611; blad
              - 3915: Bonifacio Strait, 8th December 1944 (last correction 1947), 3612; blad
              - 3931: Golfo di Napoli, 19th October 1945 (last correction 1957), 3613; blad
              - 3935: Stretto di Messina and approaches, 19th October 1945 (last correction 1958), 3614; blad
            - North Sea, The Channel, British waters, Norwegian Sea, B.2.7.3.2.3.8
              - 12: Norway to Iceland, including the Faeroes, 15th March 1915 (last correction 1961), 3615; blad
              - 26: Tor Bay - Brixham and Torquay Harbours, 5th September 1952, 3616; blad
              - 30: Plymouth Sound and Hamoaze, 30th December 1899 (last correction 1953), 3617; blad
              - 34: The Scilly Isles, 27th December 1906 (last correction 1950), 3618; blad
              - 60: Alderney and The Casquets, 14th June 1865 (last correction 1956), 3619; blad
              - 62a: Island of Jersey (eastern sheet), August, 1901 (last correction 1953), 3620; blad
              - 62b: Island of Jersey (middle sheet), 10th June 1868 (last correction 1956), 3621; blad
              - 62c: Island of Jersy (western sheet), date unknown (corrections between 1920-1954), 3622; blad
              - 97: Zeebrugge Harbour, 27th May 1924 (last correction 1963), 3623; blad
              - 108: Skegness to Blakeney including The Wash, 7th November 1958 (last correction 1961), 3624; blad
              - 109: Entrance to the river Humber, 20th February 1942 (last correction 1962), 3625; blad
              - 109: River Humber and the rivers Ouse and Trent, 14th December 1990 (revised 1996) (last correction 1997), 3626; blad
              - 114a: Firth of Forth, St. Abbs Head to the Forth Bridge, 2nd October 1860 (last correction 1938), 3627; blad
              - 114a: St. Abbs Head to The Forth Bridge, 2nd October 1860 (last correction 1958), 3628; blad
              - 114b: Fisherrow to Port Edgar, 10th June 1899 (last correction 1958), 3629; blad
              - 122: Mouths of the Maas - Hook of Holland to Goeree, 19th April 1957 (last correction 1970), 3630; blad
              - 154: Approaches to Falmouth, 6th August 1943 (last correction 1953), 3631; blad
              - 196: Nidingen to Hönö, 7th July 1874 (last correction 1951), 3632; blad
              - 219: Western approaches to the Orkneys and Shetlands, 11th April 1941 (last correction 1961), 3633; blad
              - 246: Scotland to Greenland, 26th April 1940 ((revised 1961), 3634; blad
              - 262a: Herm and Sark, date unknown (revised 1864) (last correction 1954), 3635; blad
              - 262b: Guernsey - eastern portion, and Herm, 24th December 1863 (last correction 1956), 3636; blad
              - 262c: Guernsey - western portion, date unknown (last correction 1954), 3637; blad
              - 321: Flensborg Fjord, April 1933, published by the Royal Danish Hydrographic Office in Copenhagen, 3638; blad
              - 323: Calais to Dunkerque, 12th January 1940 (revised 1961), 3639; blad
              - 329: Boulogne to Calais, 11th November 1960, 3640; blad
              - 394: The Solent - eastern part, including Spit-head, 25th June 1935 (revised 1962), 3641; blad
              - 438: Boulogne, 12th April 1968 (revised 1981) (last correction 1992), 3642; blad
              - 442: Lizard Point to Straight Point, 2nd November 1956, 3643; blad
              - 509: Blomö to Utvær including the northern channels leading to Bergen, 21st May 1895 (last correction 1960), 3644; blad
              - 509: Sognesjøen, 23rd August 1974 (last correction 1991), 3645; blad
              - 1094: Outer Gabbard to Outer Dowsing, 1st February 1912 (last correction 1937), 3646; blad
              - 1106: Approaches to Cherbourg, 10th September 1976 (revised 1985), 3647; blad
              - 1118a: Shetland Isles - sheet 1, 18th June 1884 (last correction 1960), 3648; blad
              - 1118b: Shetland Isles - sheet 2, 18th June 1884 (last correction 1960), 3649; blad
              - 1145: Vaagsö to Skorpen, 27th July 1900 (last correction 1958), 3650; blad
              - 1146: Rövde and adjacent Fjords, 27th July 1900 (last correction 1957), 3651; blad
              - 1150: River Thames - Erith to Broadness, 26th July 1963, 3652; blad
              - 1161: Swansea Bay, 21st September 1885 (last correction 1939), 3653; blad
              - 1161: Swansea Bay and approaches to Porthcawl, 7th December 1951 (last correction 1961), 3654; blad
              - 1170b: Great Ormes Head to Liverpool, 1st June 1886 (last correction 1950), 3655; blad
              - 1176: Newport and Weston-super-Mare to Chepstow and Bristol, 8th February 1928 (last correction 1953), 3656; blad
              - 1179: Bristol Channel, 9th April 1906 (last correction 1939), 3657; blad
              - 1179: Bristol Channel, 24th April 1953, 3658; blad
              - 1185: River Thames - sea reach, 5th August 1914 (last correction 1955), 3659; blad
              - 1185: River Thames - sea reach, 31st August 1962, 3660; blad
              - 1188: River Humber, Spurn Point to Immingham Dock, 24th December 1919 (last correction 1933), 3661; blad
              - 1188: River Humber - Spurn Head to Immingham Dock, 11th February 1949 (revised 1962), 3662; blad
              - 1190: Blakeney to Flamborough Head, 20th April 1890 (last correction 1947), 3663; blad
              - 1190: Blakeney to Flamborough Head, 6th July 1951 (last correction 1964), 3664; blad
              - 1192: Hartlepool to St. Abbs Head, 12th March 1879 (last correction 1952), 3665; blad
              - 1200: Hartlepool to Flamborough Head, 7th October 1960 (revised 1968), 3666; blad
              - 1267: Approaches to Plymouth, 9th January 1890 (last correction 1949), 3667; blad
              - 1267: Dodman Point to Start Point, 2nd September 1955 (revised 1962), 3668; blad
              - 1291: Nerlandsö to Lepsö including the approaches to Alesund, 13th May 1896 (last correction 1960), 3669; blad
              - 1352: Dunkirk Road, 5th February 1890 (last correction 1937), 3670; blad
              - 1404: Ardrossan Harbour, 28th May 1954 (last correction 1966), 3671; blad
              - 1405: Texel to Helgoland, 13th October 1961, 3672; blad
              - 1405: Terschelling to Esbjerg, 24th November 1989 (revised 1992) (last correction 2001), 3673; blad
              - 1409 (D6): Montrose to Banff, 3rd May 1957 (Decca chart 3rd May 1957), 3674; blad
              - 1410: Carnsore Point to Braich-y-Pwll, 30th July 1954 (last correction 1957), 3675; blad
              - 1411: Braich-y-Pwll to Clogher Head, 1st October 1954 (last correction 1957), 3676; blad
              - 1458: Bornrif tot monden van de Eems, October 1986 (revised 1990), 3677; blad
              - 1464: Menai Strait, 23rd May 1894 (last correction 1932), 3678; blad
              - 1478: Saint Govan's Head to Saint David's Head, 22nd August 1975 (revised 1984), 3679; blad
              - 1479: Lindesnes to Nordkapp, 11th July 1891 (last correction 1960), 3680; blad
              - 1481: River Tay, 5th March 1976 (revised 1989) (last correction 1992), 3681; blad
              - 1484: Plans in Cardigan Bay, 15th March 1985, 3682; blad
              - 1503: Wells to Haisborough with the off lying shoals between Outer Dowsing and Smiths Knoll, 4th December 1959 (last correction 1962), 3683; blad
              - 1504: Cromer to Harwich, 15th December 1961 (revised 1962) (last correction 1963), 3684; blad
              - 1607: Thames Estuary - southern part, 21st June 1963 (revised 1967), 3685; blad
              - 1610: North Foreland to Orfordness including the entrance to the Thames, 14th December 1933 (last correction 1951), 3686; blad
              - 1612: Harbours and anchorages on the east coast of England and Scotland, 3rd January 1975 (revised 1982), 3687; blad
              - 1652: Owers to Beachy Head, 29th October 1894 (last correction 1931), 3688; blad
              - 1662: Skudesnes Fjord and approach to Stavanger, 22nd June 1898 (last correction 1954), 3689; blad
              - 1698: Dover Harbour, 25th November 1955 (revised 1962), 3690; blad
              - 1828: The Downs, 16th November 1932 (last correction 1938), 3691; blad
              - 1843: East London Harbour and approaches, 25th May 1956 (revised 1961), 3692; blad
              - 1859: Port of Bristol, 13th July 1990 (revised 1994), 3693; blad
              - 1864: Campeltown Loch - Lamlash Harbour, 13th June 1958 (last correction 1960), 3694; blad
              - 1872: Dunkerque to Flushing, 28th December 1962 (revised 1966) (last correction 1967), 3695; blad
              - 1872: Dunkerque to Flushing, 28th December 1962 (revised 1966) (last correction 1970), 3696; blad
              - 1875: Die Jade to Norder Piep including Helgoland, 24th September 1954 (last correction 1959), 3697; blad
              - 1875: Die Jade to Norder Piep, 24th September 1954 (revised 1962) (last correction 1963), 3698; blad
              - 1895: Dover Strait, 16th October 1959 (revised 1967), 3699; blad
              - 1895: Dover Strait, 16th October 1959 (revised 1971), 3700; blad
              - 1905: Southampton Water, 15th March 1928 (last correction 1931), 3701; blad
              - 1905: Southampton Water, 12th August 1955 (revised 1963), 3702; blad
              - 1934: River Tyne Entrance, 2nd April 1954 (last correction 1956), 3703; blad
              - 1951: Liverpool Bay, 21st December 1903 (last correction 1951), 3704; blad
              - 1951: Approaches to Liverpool, 10th July 1959 (revised 1966), 3705; blad
              - 1970: Mariners' routeing guide southern North Sea, December 1986 (revised 1992), 3706; blad
              - 1970: Mariners' routeing guide southern North Sea, December 1986 (revised 2002), 3707; blad
              - 1975: Thames Estuary - northern part, 7th December 1962, 3708; blad
              - 1977: Holyhead to Great Ormes Head, 3rd February 1961 (revised 1960), 3709; blad
              - 1978: Great Ormes Head to Liverpool, 3rd February 1961, 3710; blad
              - 1981: Approaches to Preston, 31st December 1951 (last correction 1959), 3711; blad
              - 1994: Approaches to the River Clyde, 8th November 1974 (revised 1979) (last correction 1992), 3712; blad
              - 2040: The Solent - western part, 25th June 1935 (last correction 1950), 3713; blad
              - 2040: The Solent - western part, 25th June 1935 (revised 1963), 3714; blad
              - 2041: Port of Southampton, 1st March 1974 (revised 1989) (last correction 1992), 3715; blad
              - 2045: Christchurch to Owers, 20th June 1952, 3716; blad
              - 2045: Christchurch to Owers, 20th June 1952 (last correction 1956), 3717; blad
              - 2045: Christchurch to Owers, 20th June 1952 (last correction 1961), 3718; blad
              - 2050: Nab Tower to Spithead, 25th June 1935 (last correction 1952), 3719; blad
              - 2050: Eastern approaches to The Solent: Nab Tower to Spithead, 25th June 1935 (revised 1959), 3720; blad
              - 2052: The Naze to Orford Ness, 5th April 1940 (revised 1966) (last correction 1968), 3721; blad
              - 2144: Kilbrannan Sound and approaches, 8th October 1943 (revised 1959) (last correction 1960), 3722; blad
              - 2146: Approaches to Le Havre, Dives to Cap d'Antifer, 21st July 1961, 3723; blad
              - 2151: River Thames - Broadness to Mucking Flats, 3rd April 1939 (last correction 1958), 3724; blad
              - 2154: Newhaven, 24th February 1888 (last correction 1931), 3725; blad
              - 2159: Firth of Clyde and Loch Fyne, 12th January 1869 (last correction 1936), 3726; blad
              - 2159: Firth of Clyde and approaches, 12th January 1869 (last correction 1960), 3727; blad
              - 2164: Firth of Clyde, Bennane Head to Largs Channel, 21st April 1944 (revised 1959) (last correction 1961), 3728; blad
              - 2179: Orkney Islands - southern sheet, 23rd June 1961, 3729; blad
              - 2181: Texel to Bergen including The Skaw, 31st May 1940 (last correction 1956), 3730; blad
              - 2181: Texel to Bergen including The Skaw, 31st May 1940 (revised 1961), 3731; blad
              - 2182a: North Sea - southern sheet, 8th November 1920 (revised 1961), 3732; blad
              - 2182a: The North Sea - southern sheet, 8th November 1920 (last correction 1955), 3733; blad
              - 2182b (D6): The North Sea - central sheet, 26th July 1921 (last correction 1958) (Decca chart 20th April 1956), 3734; blad
              - 2182b: North Sea - central sheet, 26th July 1921 (revised 1961), 3735; blad
              - 2182b: The North Sea - central sheet, 26th July 1921 (revised 1961) (last correction 1963), 3736; blad
              - 2182c: North Sea - northern sheet, 4th May 1915 (revised 1960), 3737; blad
              - 2182d: Faeroe Islands to Norway, 28th January 1918 (last correction 1960), 3738; blad
              - 2219: Western approaches to The Solent including Needles Channel and Christchurch Bay, 25th June 1935 (last correction 1953), 3739; blad
              - 2228: Lofoten Islands to Vest-Spitsbergen - Björnöya, 19th June 1930 (revised 1961), 3740; blad
              - 2255: Weymouth and Portland, 14th December 1945 (last correction 1954), 3741; blad
              - 2255: Weymouth and Portland, 14th December 1945 (revised 1963), 3742; blad
              - 2268: Portland Harbour and Coaling Piers, 4th August 1939 (last correction 1953), 3743; blad
              - 2290: Exmouth Harbour - Teignmouth, 1st April 1960, 3744; blad
              - 2291: Bergen to Stav Fjord, 8th June 1874 (last correction 1957), 3745; blad
              - 2303: Approaches to Bergen, 21st May 1894 (last correction 1960), 3746; blad
              - 2304: Karmö to Bergen, 18th June 1873 (last correction 1961), 3747; blad
              - 2305: Stav Fjord to Harö Fjord, 24th March 1881 (last correction 1959), 3748; blad
              - 2306: Harøyfjorden to Hitra, 17th April 1855 (last correction 1960), 3749; blad
              - 2307: Smøla to Sves Fjord, 10th March 1920 (last correction 1960), 3750; blad
              - 2308: Brands Fjord to Leka, 10th April 1855 (last correction 1959), 3751; blad
              - 2309: Leka to Dönna, April 1855 (last correction 1960), 3752; blad
              - 2310: Dönna to Fleina, 12th October 1921 (last correction 1961), 3753; blad
              - 2311: Fleina to Tranøy with part of Lofoten Islands, 8th July 1918 (last correction 1960), 3754; blad
              - 2312: Lofoten Islands to Andöy, 10th July 1918 (last correction 1960), 3755; blad